goseek.com 2016-08-27

# goSeek.com | Hotel Discounts, Deals, and Special Offers

Privacy Policy 

Introduction 

Thank you for using the goSeek website and other applications (the “Service”), which are provided by DealBase Corporation. The terms “we”, “us”, “our”, “goSeek”, and “DealBase” refer to DealBase Corporation, a Delaware Corporation and/or our subsidiaries. The term “you” refers to the customer using our Service. 

Now on to the Privacy Policy! At goSeek, we want to help you find the very best value when you purchase travel online. In order to do so, we need to ensure that you feel comfortable using our Service. Our Privacy Policy is here to help in that regard. It will address questions that you might have related to what information we collect, how we collect it, and how we use it. It also provides instructions on how to remove your information from our Service should you so choose, or how to update it. We want this Privacy Policy to be clear and useful. Please send us feedback here [contactus@goseek.com](mailto:contactus@goseek.com) if you feel that it is not in any way. By using our Service, you are indicating to us that you agree to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

What information we collect 

Information you provide 

If you use our Service to search travel, we receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. This might include information about you (“personal information”) including your name, email address, and zip code. We will also store a username and password, should you choose to create an account directly with us at any time. We also receive and store information related to your travel searches on our site, including your destination, dates, and other attributes such as number of rooms and number of occupants. 

Third party login information 

Currently, goSeek allows users with accounts on third party services such as Facebook and Google to register and log into our Service using functionality that those third party services provide. By using this functionality to log into our Service, you permit us to retrieve, store, and use specific identifying information related to your accounts with these third party services. This information includes items such as your first name, last name, email address, and your location (if you have provided it to them). 

“Automatically collected” information 

We automatically collect some information about your device when you visit goSeek. For example, we will collect your IP address and information related to your operating system and web browsing software (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Apple Safari, or Mozilla Firefox, as well as version numbers). We may also collect information about your online activity, such as pages viewed, time on site, and number of clicks. Our goal in collecting this information is to help improve and customize your experience with our Service. 

Cookies and other similar web technologies 

We use several common web tracking tools to help identify you and collect usage information as you use our Service over time and across different platforms. We also work with third parties that collect and use information this way. The tools we use include “cookies” (a small piece of data that a web server places in a file on your computer) and “web beacons” (single pixel GIF images that are placed in the code of a web page or in an email newsletter). If you are concerned about our use of these technologies, most web browsers provide users the ability to limit the use of cookies and web beacons by adjusting their privacy settings. 

How we use that information 

In general 

We use the information that you provide to better tailor our experience to you and your needs, so that our Service becomes inherently more useful over time. 

Email address 

We will use your email address to give you updates on how our Service is evolving, as well as to provide you with promotional materials and offers, should you give us permission. It is our goal to have promotions be useful and relevant to you, and we want them to become increasingly so over time. 

Cookies and other similar web technologies 

We use web tracking tools such as cookies and web beacons for the following purposes 

  1. To distinguish new versus returning users to our Service 
  2. To help remember specific information about you from a prior visit to our Service so that we can better customize our site to meet your needs 
  3. To work with online advertising companies to display targeted advertising on our Service and other third party services that you might visit. This targeting may be based on information you provide to us or your browsing behavior while using our Service. It may also be based on your browsing behavior on other services. We may also obtain browsing history and other demographic information about you from our partners in order to better target advertising displayed while you are using our Service. When we show you advertising on goSeek, it is our hope that it will be useful and relevant. Our use of cookies and web beacons is only to help support that goal. If you are uncomfortable with targeted advertising, there are mechanisms to opt out of it. For more information, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

How we share information with others 

We may freely share personally identifiable information among companies that are subsidiaries or affiliates of the DealBase Corporation. 

We may provide personally identifiable information to third parties who help us perform critical internal business functions, as permitted by law. These third parties perform services on our behalf and have agreed in writing to protect and not further disclose your information. As an example, we work with a third party to send all of our emails, and as part of that process provide them with your email address, location, and the content of the email to be sent. 

We may provide aggregated, non-personally identifiable information to third parties for various purposes. As an example, we work with a third party to help us analyze user behavior on our web site, and as part of that process we provide them with your browsing behavior while using our Service. 

We may share your information as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. As an example, if you provide us information in order to enter a sweepstakes that we sponsor with a partner, we may share your information with that partner. 

We may also disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) satisfy legal obligations or comply with a legal process that involves goSeek (2) protect goSeek from fraudulent, abusive, predatory, or unlawful uses of our Service (3) investigate and defend goSeek from any legal claims or threats (4) protect the rights and property of goSeek or (5) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of the public. 

In each of the cases above, information may be securely transmitted to and stored by a third party on servers that they own and operate. 

If there is a change in ownership of goSeek, including through a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to any other entity, we may sell or otherwise transfer all the information that you have provided to us, including personally identifiable information, to that entity. 

How you can access and update your information 

You can manage your account settings in the “My Account” section on goSeek. If you have used a third party such as Facebook or Google to log into goSeek, you will need to go to the account settings section of those websites to view your information. 

Choices you have regarding your information 

  1. You can delete your goSeek account at any time with a single click from the “My Account” section of our website 
  2. You can unsubscribe from one or more email newsletters via the “My Account” section of our website, or by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email 
  3. You can write us at the following address to request that we delete your account or unsubscribe you from promotional emails. 

goSeek, a service of Dealbase Corporation   
2831 St. Rose Parkway, Suite 200   
Henderson, NV 89052 

External links and other websites 

We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites that may be linked to our Service, or of any third party advertisers. When leave the goSeek Service, our privacy policy no longer applies. 

Children’s privacy 

Our age restrictions for our Service are set forth in our Terms of Use. We do not target any portion of our Service to children under the age of 13. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we may receive from users we believe to be under the age of 13 will be purged from our database. 

Visiting our website from outside the United States 

If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to and stored on servers residing in the United States, where we operate. The data protection and privacy laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but do know that we do take steps pursuant to the laws of the United States to ensure that your privacy is protected. 

Your California privacy rights 

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at the address provided below in the “How you can contact us” section. 

How you can contact us 

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us via email at contactus@goseek.com or via mail at: 

goSeek, a service of Dealbase Corporation   
2831 St. Rose Parkway, Suite 200   
Henderson, NV 89052 

Changes to this policy 

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time in the future. If and when we do so, we will update the effective date below. Any revisions will take effect upon posting. If there are material changes to this policy, we will notify you via the email address that you provided to us and/or by placing a notice on our website. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy from time to time to review the most current version. 

Effective date 

August 27, 2016
